<?xml version="1.0" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
    <author>w33zl</author>
    <version>2.0.0.2-beta</version>
    <title>
        <en>PowerTools</en>
    </title>
    <contributors>Translations: Lactic, nagor</contributors>
    <description>
<en><![CDATA[
With the PowerTools (a.k.a. "the F12 mod") you have quick and easy access to some "quality of life" features. Especially useful if you are a modder or do mod reviews.

Using a single key/button (configurable, default F12) you activate the PowerTools menu. From there you can quickly navigate to the different functions without the need for a mouse or navigating through multiple menus.

MAIN FEATURES:
- Add/remove money to your farm
- Fill vehicle - supports vehicles with multiple tanks/storage units and accepts any filltype supported by the vehicle !
- Spawn any type of pallet (including production materials like sugar and clothes) !
- Spawn any type of bale - supports round/square, all sizes and all types (straw, silage, cotton etc) !
- Spawn tree logs - currently only supports birch, spruce and pine (in a limited number of lengths) !
- [DISABLED*] Quickly save the current game, ether via hotkey or the menu !
- [DISABLED*] Quickly exit current game and go to the main menu (or restart the savegame, see below)
- [DISABLED*] Toggle "Flight mode" (then use J to activate flight mode and Q/E to ascend/descend in the air)
- [DISABLED*] Toggle HUD/interface on/off
- [DISABLED*] Toggle "Super strength" mode
- Repeat last command

Please note:
1. Features marked with an asterisk (*) are currently disabled due to breaking changes in FS25. If/when Giants re-enable the underlying support for these features, they will be re-enabled in the mod.
2. Features marked with an asterisk (!) isn't available on dedicated servers, only in singleplayer and self-hosted multiplayer.

NOTES:
- To reset your money (or set to a specific amount) use '=' as a prefix, e.g. '=100' would set your bank account to 100
- Many of the features requires that you have admin access (to prevent cheating in multiplayer) - in single player everyone is admin though :)
- Filling vehicles, saving the game and spawning bales/pallets/trees currently only work if you are the host of the game (i.e. single player or self-hosted multiplayer) and does not work on dedicated servers
- To be able to use "Repeat last action" you need to bind a hotkey in the input binding settings (i.e. this feature has no default key binding)

CHANGELOG:
v2.0:
- NEW: FS25 support
]]></en>

<de><![CDATA[


]]></de>

<fr><![CDATA[

   
]]></fr>

    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_PowerTools.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <l10n filenamePrefix="language" />
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="lib/LogHelper.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="lib/ModHelper.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="PowerTools.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="POWERTOOLSMENU">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_f12"/>
		</actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>

    <actions>
        <action name="POWERTOOLSMENU" />
        <action name="POWERTOOLS_QUICKSAVE" />
        <action name="POWERTOOLS_REPEAT_ACTION" />
	</actions>

</modDesc>