<?xml version="1.0" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="93">
    <author>w33zl</author>
    <version>1.0.1.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>PowerTools</en>
    </title>
    <contributors>Translations: Lactic, nagor, Luan Tavares, Lang_Alpayx, Pericops, SniperKittenCZ</contributors>
    <description>
<en><![CDATA[
With the PowerTools menu you have quick and easy access to some "quality of life" features. Especially useful if you are a modder or content creator.

Using a single key/button (default F12) you activate the PowerTools menu. From there you can quickly navigate to the different functions without the need for a mouse or navigating through multiple menus.

MAIN FEATURES:
- Add/remove money to your farm
- Fill vehicle - supports vehicles with multiple tanks/storage units and accepts any filltype supported by the vehicle *
- Spawn any type of pallet (including production materials like sugar and clothes) *
- Spawn any type of bale - supports round/square, all sizes and all types (straw, silage, cotton etc) *
- Spawn tree logs - currently only supports limited number of lengths *
- Toggle super speed, super strength or flight mode
- Quickly save the current game, ether via hotkey or the menu *
- Toggle HUD/interface on/off
- Repeat last command
- Open PowerTools menu in alternate mode (restart and exit to menu uses the "hard reset" method instead of "soft reset")
- A limited PowerTools menu can now be opened when main menu is open as well as when the game is paused

NOTES: 
1. Features marked with an asterisk (*) isn't available on dedicated servers, only in singleplayer and self-hosted multiplayer.
2. Many of the features requires that you have admin access (to prevent cheating in multiplayer) - in single player everyone is admin though :)
3. To be able to use "Repeat last action" you need to bind a hotkey in the input binding settings
4. The new alternate mode menu uses a separate hotkey (default Right Ctrl + F12)

CHANGELOG:
v1.0.1:
- HOTFIX: Pallet spawning should now work for all players (no matter how you start the game)
- FIX: Choice of pallets is not reset (as intended, i.e. you can now spawn multiple pallets in a row)
- FIX: Removed false error message when spawning pallets
]]></en>

<de><![CDATA[
Mit dem Menü "PowerTools" haben Sie schnellen und einfachen Zugriff auf einige "Lebensqualitäts"-Funktionen. Dies ist besonders nützlich, wenn Sie Modder oder Inhaltsersteller sind.

Mit einer einzigen Taste (standardmäßig F12) aktivieren Sie das Menü "PowerTools". Von dort aus können Sie schnell zu den verschiedenen Funktionen navigieren, ohne dass Sie eine Maus benötigen oder sich durch mehrere Menüs bewegen müssen.

HAUPTMERKMALE:
- Hinzufügen/Entfernen von Geld zu Ihrer Farm
- Fahrzeug befüllen - unterstützt Fahrzeuge mit mehreren Tanks/Lagereinheiten und akzeptiert jeden vom Fahrzeug unterstützten Fülltyp *
- Jede Art von Palette erzeugen (einschließlich Produktionsmaterialien wie Zucker und Kleidung) *
- Jede Art von Ballen erzeugen - unterstützt rund/quadratisch, alle Größen und alle Arten (Stroh, Silage, Baumwolle usw.) *
- Baumstämme erzeugen - unterstützt derzeit nur eine begrenzte Anzahl von Längen *
- Umschalten zwischen Supergeschwindigkeit, Superstärke und Flugmodus
- Schnelles Speichern des aktuellen Spiels, entweder per Hotkey oder über das Menü *
- HUD/Interface ein-/ausschalten
- Wiederholen des letzten Befehls
- Öffnen des PowerTools-Menüs im alternativen Modus (Neustart und Verlassen des Menüs mit der „Hard Reset“-Methode anstelle von „Soft Reset“)
- Ein eingeschränktes PowerTools-Menü kann nun geöffnet werden, wenn das Hauptmenü geöffnet ist und wenn das Spiel pausiert wird.

HINWEISE: 
1. Die mit einem Sternchen (*) gekennzeichneten Funktionen sind nicht auf dedizierten Servern verfügbar, sondern nur im Einzelspielermodus und im selbstgehosteten Mehrspielermodus.
2. Viele der Features erfordern einen Admin-Zugang (um Cheating im Multiplayer zu verhindern) - im Singleplayer ist allerdings jeder Admin :)
3. Um die Funktion „Letzte Aktion wiederholen“ nutzen zu können, muss man einen Hotkey in den Einstellungen für die Eingabe binden
4. Das neue Menü für den alternativen Modus verwendet einen separaten Hotkey (standardmäßig Rechts Strg + F12)

CHANGELOG:
v1.0.1:
- HOTFIX: Das Spawnen von Paletten sollte jetzt für alle Spieler funktionieren (unabhängig davon, wie man das Spiel startet)
- FIX: Die Auswahl der Paletten wird nicht zurückgesetzt (wie vorgesehen, d.h. man kann jetzt mehrere Paletten hintereinander spawnen)
- FIX: Falsche Fehlermeldung beim Spawnen von Paletten beseitigt
]]></de>

<fr><![CDATA[
Le menu Outils vous permet d'accéder rapidement et facilement à certaines fonctions de "qualité de vie". C'est particulièrement utile si vous êtes un moddeur ou un créateur de contenu.

Une seule touche/bouton (par défaut F12) vous permet d'activer le menu Power Tools. À partir de là, vous pouvez naviguer rapidement vers les différentes fonctions sans avoir besoin d'une souris ou de naviguer dans plusieurs menus.

CARACTÉRISTIQUES PRINCIPALES :
- Ajouter/supprimer de l'argent à votre ferme
- Remplir un véhicule - supporte les véhicules avec plusieurs réservoirs/unités de stockage et accepte tout type de remplissage supporté par le véhicule *
- Créer n'importe quel type de palette (y compris les matériaux de production comme le sucre et les vêtements) *
- Produire n'importe quel type de balles - rondes ou carrées, de toutes tailles et de tous types (paille, ensilage, coton, etc.) *
- Produire des troncs d'arbres - pour l'instant, seul un nombre limité de longueurs est pris en charge *
- Changement de la super vitesse, de la super force ou du mode de vol
- Sauvegarde rapide de la partie en cours, soit par le raccourci clavier, soit par le menu *
- Activer/désactiver le HUD/interface
- Répéter la dernière commande
- Ouvrir le menu PowerTools en mode alternatif (le redémarrage et la sortie du menu utilisent la méthode « hard reset » au lieu de « soft reset »).
- Un menu PowerTools limité peut maintenant être ouvert lorsque le menu principal est ouvert ainsi que lorsque le jeu est en pause.

NOTES : 
1. Les fonctions marquées d'un astérisque (*) ne sont pas disponibles sur les serveurs dédiés, seulement en mode solo et en mode multijoueur auto-hébergé.
2. Beaucoup de fonctionnalités nécessitent un accès administrateur (pour éviter la triche en multijoueur) - en solo, tout le monde est administrateur :)
3. Pour pouvoir utiliser « Répéter la dernière action », vous devez lier un raccourci clavier dans les paramètres de liaison d'entrée.
4. Le nouveau menu du mode alternatif utilise un raccourci-clavier séparé (par défaut Ctrl + F12).

CHANGELOG :
v1.0.1 :
- HOTFIX : L'apparition des palettes devrait maintenant fonctionner pour tous les joueurs (quelle que soit la façon dont vous démarrez le jeu).
- FIXE : Le choix des palettes n'est pas réinitialisé (comme prévu, c'est à dire que vous pouvez maintenant faire apparaître plusieurs palettes à la suite).
- FIXE : Suppression du message d'erreur erroné lors de la création de palettes.
]]></fr>

<cz><![CDATA[
Pomocí nabídky PowerTools máte rychlý a snadný přístup k některým funkcím „kvality života“. Zvláště užitečné, pokud jste modder nebo tvůrce obsahu.

Pomocí jediné klávesy/tlačítka (výchozí F12) aktivujete nabídku PowerTools. Odtud můžete rychle přejít k různým funkcím, aniž byste potřebovali myš nebo procházeli více nabídkami.

HLAVNÍ VLASTNOSTI:
- Přidejte / odeberte peníze na svou farmu
- Plnění vozidel - podporuje vozidla s více nádržemi/úložnými jednotkami a přijímá jakýkoli typ plnění podporovaný vozidlem *
- Spawnujte jakýkoli typ palety (včetně výrobních materiálů, jako je cukr a oblečení) *
- Spawnujte jakýkoli typ balíku - podporuje kulaté/čtvercové, všechny velikosti a všechny typy (sláma, siláž, bavlna atd.) *
- Spawnujte klády - v současné době podporuje pouze omezený počet délek *
- Přepněte super rychlost, super sílu nebo letový režim
- Rychle uložte aktuální hru, buď pomocí klávesové zkratky nebo nabídky *
- Zapnutí/vypnutí HUD/rozhraní
- Opakujte poslední příkaz
- Otevřete nabídku PowerTools v alternativním režimu (restart a návrat do nabídky používá metodu "hard reset" místo "soft reset")
- Omezené menu PowerTools lze nyní otevřít, když je otevřeno hlavní menu, stejně jako když je hra pozastavena

POZNÁMKY:
1. Funkce označené hvězdičkou (*) nejsou dostupné na vyhrazených serverech, pouze v singleplayeru a multiplayeru s vlastním hostitelem.
2. Mnoho funkcí vyžaduje, abyste měli administrátorský přístup (abyste zabránili podvádění v multiplayeru) - v singleplayeru je ale každý administrátor :)
3. Abyste mohli použít "Opakovat poslední akci", musíte svázat klávesovou zkratku v nastavení vazby vstupu
4. Nová nabídka alternativního režimu používá samostatnou klávesovou zkratku (výchozí pravý Ctrl + F12)

]]></cz>



    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_PowerTools.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <l10n filenamePrefix="language" />
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="lib/LogHelper.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="lib/ModHelper.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="PowerTools.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="POWERTOOLSMENU">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_f12"/>
		</actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="POWERTOOLSMENU_ALTERNATIVE">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_f12"/>
		</actionBinding>        
    </inputBinding>

    <actions>
        <action name="POWERTOOLSMENU" />
        <action name="POWERTOOLSMENU_ALTERNATIVE" />
        <action name="POWERTOOLS_QUICKSAVE" />
        <action name="POWERTOOLS_REPEAT_ACTION" />
        <action name="POWERTOOLS_TOGGLE_MODES" />
	</actions>

</modDesc>